Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6, 1.
  - District 6 Vice President Michael Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, October 1, 1941 - October 24, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 10, 1945; 15. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 15)
    - Emspak Regarding Reconversion, Political Action, Organization and Factionalism, May 9, 1945; 16. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 16)
    - Emspak Regarding West Virginia CIO with October 22, 1945, John Easton Letter to UE, October 24, 1945; 17. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 17)
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 615 and Factionalism with Fitzgerald Letter to William Tunny, July 15, 1943; 18. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 18)
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Local 615, March 22, 1944; 19. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 19)
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Reservation, April 3, 1945; 20. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 20)
    - Fitzgerald Telegram Regarding Appointments, September 10, 1945; 21. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 21)
    - Tom Flanagan Regarding Staff Finances, October 1, 1941; 22. (Box 2, Folder 51, Item 22)
  - District 6 Vice President Michael Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, January 29 - October 31, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - James Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Westinghouse Airbrake, January 29, 1941; 1. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 1)
    - Matles Regarding Local 613, February 6, 1941; 2. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 2)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 28, 1941; 3. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 3)
    - Secretary to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 28, 1941; 4. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 4)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 3, 1941; 5. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 5)
    - Secretary to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 15, 1941; 6. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 6)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 18, 1941; 7. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 7)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 13, 1941; 8. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 8)
    - Agnes Quinn, Secretary to Matles, Regarding Local 615, May 15, 1941; 9. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 9)
    - Matles Regarding UE News, June 2, 1941; 10. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 10)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 23, 1941; 11. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 11)
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, July 23, 1941; 12. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 12)
    - Matles Regarding Sharon Westinghouse Organization, July 24, 1941; 13. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 13)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members with August 11, 1941, Eugene Kraus Letter to Matles, August 14, 1941; 14. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 14)
    - Matles Regarding St. Mary's Organization, September 18, 1941; 15. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 15)
    - Matles Regarding White Collar Workers and East Pittsburgh Westinghouse, September 22, 1941; 16. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 16)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members and St. Mary's Organization, September 23, 1941; 17. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 17)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members and St. Mary's Organization, October 1, 1941; 18. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 18)
    - Matles Letter, October 1, 1941; 19. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 19)
    - Matles Regarding Pittsburgh Organization and White Collar Workers, October 7, 1941; 20. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 20)
    - Matles Regarding Fairmont Westinghouse Organization, October 8, 1941; 21. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 21)
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, October 17, 1941; 22. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 22)
    - Secretary to Matles Letter, October 21, 1941; 23. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 23)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 22, 1941; 24. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 24)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, October 29, 1941; 25. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 25)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 31, 1941; 26. (Box 2, Folder 52, Item 26)
  - District 6 Vice President Michael Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, November 12, 1941 - February 8, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - James Matles Regarding Bridgeville General Electric, November 12, 1941; 1. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 1)
    - Matles Regarding Organization, December 12, 1941; 2. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 2)
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, January 2, 1942; 3. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 3)
    - Matles Regarding Finances, January 27, 1942; 4. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 4)
    - Matles Regarding Finances, February 4, 1942; 5. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 5)
    - Matles Regarding Mesta Machine and United Steelworkers of America, February 12, 1942; 6. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 6)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 18, 1942; 7. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 7)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 5, 1942; 8. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 8)
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, March 13, 1942; 9. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 9)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 14, 1942; 10. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 10)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 13, 1942; 11. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 11)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 12, 1942; 12. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 12)
    - Norma Gould, Secretary to Matles, Regarding Staff Members, May 14, 1942; 13. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 13)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 11, 1942; 14. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 14)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 29, 1942; 15. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 15)
    - Matles Regarding Finances and Staff Members, September 22, 1942; 16. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 16)
    - Matles Regarding Meetings and Staff Members, June 18, 1943; 17. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 17)
    - Matles Regarding Finances, June 21, 1943; 18. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 18)
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Meeting, July 8, 1943; 19. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 19)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 28, 1943; 20. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 20)
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Reservations, July 8, 1943; 21. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 21)
    - Matles Regarding Organization, August 3, 1943; 22. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 22)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 11, 1943; 23. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 23)
    - Matles Telegram, Undated; 24. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 24)
    - Matles Regarding Finances, Undated; 25. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 25)
    - Edward Matthews Letter, August 17, 1943; 26. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 26)
    - Allan McNeil Regarding Staff Members, February 8, 1944; 27. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 27)
    - William Sentner Letter with Letter to William Chambers Regarding Staff Members, October 5, 1943; 28. (Box 2, Folder 53, Item 28)
  - District 6 Vice President Michael Fitzpatrick Outgoing Correspondence, October 29, 1940 - October 28, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Fitzpatrick to James Carey Regarding Labor's Non-Partisan League and Factionalism, October 29, 1940; 1. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 1)
    - Fitzpatrick to Carey Regarding Supplies with October 31, 1940, Spencer Thomas Letter to Fitzpatrick, November 1, 1940; 2. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 2)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Carey Regarding Local 610 Meeting, November 13, 1940; 3. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 3)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to James Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference and Wages, November 24, 1940; 4. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 4)
    - Fitzpatrick to Carey Regarding Labor's Non-Partisan League and Factionalism, November 26, 1940; 5. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 5)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Carey Regarding District 6 Executive Board Meeting, January 7, 1941; 6. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 6)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding District 6 Executive Board Meeting, January 7, 1941; 7. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 7)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 4, 1941; 8. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 8)
    - Fitzpatrick to Carey Regarding Factionalism and Local 615, March 5, 1941; 9. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 9)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 26, 1941; 10. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 10)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 11, 1941; 11. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 11)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 15, 1941; 12. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 12)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Ernie and St. Mary's Organization, May 6, 1941; 13. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 13)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Address, May 3, 1941; 14. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 14)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 23, 1941; 15. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 15)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 1941; 16. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 16)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Finances, July 22, 1941; 17. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 17)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Meeting, September 10, 1941; 18. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 18)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 15, 1941; 19. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 19)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding White Collar Workers, September 19, 1941; 20. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 20)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 29, 1941; 21. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 21)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 9, 1941; 22. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 22)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 20, 1941; 23. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 23)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 20, 1941; 24. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 24)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, October 21, 1941; 25. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 25)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 28, 1941; 26. (Box 2, Folder 54, Item 26)
  - District 6 Vice President Michael Fitzpatrick Outgoing Correspondence, October 28, 1941 - August 7, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Fitzpatrick to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 28, 1941; 1. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 1)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 30, 1941; 2. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 2)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 25, 1941; 3. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 3)
    - Fitzpatrick to Philip Murray Regarding CIO and AFL, January 22, 1942; 4. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 4)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Finances, January 23, 1942; 5. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 5)
    - Fitzpatrick to Sidney Hillman Regarding War Production Conference, January 23, 1942; 6. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 6)
    - Fitzpatrick to Edmund C. Stone Regarding Pittsburgh Defense Council Organization, January 28, 1942; 7. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 7)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Finances, January 30, 1942; 8. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 8)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 623, February 30, 1942; 9. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 9)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Local 623, March 2, 1942; 10. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 10)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 4, 1942; 11. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 11)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Sharon Organization, New Castle and Meadville, March 4, 1942; 12. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 12)
    - Fitzpatrick to Donald Nelson Regarding War Production, March 12, 1942; 13. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 13)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Finances, March 19, 1942; 14. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 14)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 10, 1942; 15. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 15)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 28, 1942; 16. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 16)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 12, 1942; 17. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 17)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 27, 1942; 18. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 18)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 17, 1942; 19. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 19)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Resolution, July 3, 1942; 20. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 20)
    - Fitzpatrick to Julius Emspak Regarding Resolution, July 3, 1942; 21. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 21)
    - Fitzpatrick to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Resolution, July 3, 1942; 22. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 22)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Sunbury Westinghouse and Jurisdiction, July 6, 1942; 23. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 23)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Attached Mailing List, July 28, 1942; 24. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 24)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Proposed Joint Labor Conference, August 7, 1942; 25. (Box 2, Folder 55, Item 25)
  - District 6 Vice President Michael Fitzpatrick Outgoing Correspondence, August 14, 1942 - June 9, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Fitzpatrick to James Matles Regarding Local 601 with "Lets Look at the Record" Leaflet, August 14, 1942; 1. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 1)
    - Fitzpatrick to Julius Emspak Regarding Meeting, December 2, 1942; 2. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 2)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Minutes, December 31, 1942; 3. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 3)
    - Fitzpatrick to L. B. F. Raycroft Regarding War Manpower Commission, January 7, 1943; 4. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 4)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 1, 1943; 5. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 5)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 19, 1943; 6. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 6)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Local 602, May 28, 1943; 7. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 7)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Finances, June 2, 1943; 8. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 8)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 15, 1943; 9. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 9)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Meeting, June 15, 1943; 10. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 10)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Hamilton Westinghouse, July 6, 1943; 11. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 11)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Matles Regarding Reservations, July 10, 1943; 12. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 12)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Hamilton Westinghouse Organization, July 21, 1943; 13. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 13)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Staff Members, Westmoreland County Sylvania Electric Products Organization, and Locals 622, 610, and 502, September 3, 1943; 14. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 14)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 615, September 14, 1943; 15. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 15)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 615, October 11, 1943; 16. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 16)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 10, 1943; 17. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 17)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Local 615 and Equitable Meter Company Negotiations in Pittsburgh, November 30, 1943; 18. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 18)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 6, 1944; 19. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 19)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 615, January 19, 1944; 20. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 20)
    - Fitzpatrick to Philip Murray Regarding Resolution and President Roosevelt Message, January 25, 1944; 21. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 21)
    - Fitzpatrick to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, April 11, 1945; 22. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 22)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, April 11, 1945; 23. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 23)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, May 21, 1945; 24. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 24)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, June 9, 1945; 25. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 25)
    - Fitzpatrick to Heck Confer Regarding Contract with C. G. Memo to Ben; January 12, 1950, Fitzpatrick Letter to UE Members Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry; and January 12, 1950, Carey Telegram Regarnding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, December 30, 1949; 26. (Box 2, Folder 56, Item 26)
  - District 6 Vice President Thomas Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, November 2, 1945 - July 3, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 2, 1945; 1. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 1)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 15, 1945; 2. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 2)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 11, 1946; 3. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 3)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 4, 1946; 4. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 4)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 18, 1946; 5. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 5)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 14, 1946; 6. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 6)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 22, 1946; 7. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 7)
    - Barish Regarding Political Action Committee, August 4, 1947; 8. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 8)
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 10, 1947; 9. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 9)
    - Barish Telegram Regarding Reservations, January 17, 1950; 10. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 10)
    - William Cahn Regarding Summer School, April 29, 1947; 11. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 11)
    - Cahn Regarding Radio Broadcasts, June 13, 1947; 12. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 12)
    - Cahn Regarding PAC, July 3, 1947; 13. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 13)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 18, 1945; 14. (Box 2, Folder 57, Item 14)
  - District 6 Vice President Thomas Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, February 6, 1946 - June 18, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Unemployment Compensation and General Electric and Westinghouse Strikes, February 6, 1946; 1. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 1)
    - Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, March 27, 1946; 2. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 2)
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Reservations, April 3, 1946; 3. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 3)
    - Emspak Regarding General Electric and Westinghouse Strikes and National Federation for Constitutional Liberties, April 4, 1946; 4. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 4)
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 3, 1946; 5. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 5)
    - Ray Klausner, Secretary to Emspak, Telegram Regarding Reservation with Letter to Mr. Crawford, June 10, 1946; 6. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 6)
    - Klausner, Secretary to Emspak, Telegram Regarding Reservations, June 17, 1946; 7. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 7)
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 25, 1946; 8. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 8)
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, July 26, 1946; 9. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 9)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, August 21, 1946; 10. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 10)
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, October 18, 1946; 11. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 11)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Locals 629 and 637, December 4, 1946; 12. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 12)
    - Emspak Regarding Local 630, January 8, 1947; 13. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 13)
    - Emspak Regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations' National Negro Congress, January 27, 1947; 14. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 14)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Per Capita Dues, January 28, 1947; 15. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 15)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Per Capita Dues, March 12, 1947; 16. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 16)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local Constitutions, March 12, 1947; 17. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 17)
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Finances, March 31, 1947; 18. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 18)
    - Emspak Regarding District Summer School, April 30, 1947; 19. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 19)
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 5, 1947; 20. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 20)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 12, 1947; 21. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 21)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, Radio Broadcasts and Local 633, May 26, 1947; 22. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 22)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 605, June 12, 1947; 23. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 23)
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Statement, June 18, 1947; 24. (Box 2, Folder 58, Item 24)
  - District 6 Vice President Thomas Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, October 30, 1945 - March 3, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Dismissals with July 1947 Charles Daugherty Letter and Emspak's Response, July 17, 1947; 1. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 1)
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local Constitutions, November 20, 1947; 2. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 2)
    - Emspak Regarding Area Meetings, December 15, 1947; 3. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 3)
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 602 and 638 Mailing Lists, January 14, 1948; 4. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 4)
    - Secretary to Albert Fitzgerald Letter, December 31, 1946; 5. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 5)
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District Constitutions, May 6, 1947; 6. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 6)
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District Summer School, May 7, 1947; 7. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 7)
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Local 601, August 26, 1947; 8. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 8)
    - James Matles Telegram Regarding Staff Members, October 30, 1945; 9. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 9)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, November 23, 1945; 10. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 10)
    - Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board and 1946 UE Convention, January 3, 1946; 11. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 11)
    - Matles Letter, January 5, 1946; 12. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 12)
    - Selma Kaslick, Secretary to Matles, Regarding Reservations, February 16, 1946; 13. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 13)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, July 1, 1946; 14. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 14)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 5, 1946; 15. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 15)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances and Local 633, November 6, 1946; 16. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 16)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 10, 1946; 17. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 17)
    - Matles Regarding Local 601, December 12, 1946; 18. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 18)
    - Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, January 16, 1947; 19. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 19)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 3, 1947; 20. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 20)
    - Matles Regarding Organizers Reports with Matles Letters to Charles Newell and All Field Organizers, March 6, 1947; 21. (Box 2, Folder 59, Item 21)
  - District 6 Vice President Thomas Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - James Matles Regarding District Summer School, May 20, 1947; 1. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 1)
    - Selma Trauber, Secretary to Matles, Letter, June 9, 1947; 2. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 2)
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 12, 1947; 3. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 3)
    - Matles Regarding Local 602 and Factionalism, November 10, 1947; 4. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 4)
    - Matles Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, October 18, 1951; 5. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 5)
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Finances, undated; 6. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 6)
    - David Ratner Regarding Finances, December 24, 1945; 7. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 7)
    - Bookkeeping Memo Regarding Staff Finances with October 24, 1946, District 6 Memo to James Kennedy, October 21, 1946; 8. (Box 2, Folder 60, Item 8)
  - District 6 Vice President Thomas Fitzpatrick Outgoing Correspondence, October 11, 1945 - December 6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Fitzpatrick to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Memo, October 11, 1945; 1. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 1)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 15, 1945; 2. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 2)
    - Fitzpatrick to Emspak Regarding Local 615 and Finances, October 24, 1945; 3. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 3)
    - Fitzpatrick to Frederick Livingston Regarding Staff Finances, November 5, 1945; 4. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 4)
    - Fitzpatrick to Nat Geller Regarding Staff Finances, November 14, 1945; 5. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 5)
    - Fitzpatrick to David Schribner Regarding Staff Finances, December 3, 1945; 6. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 6)
    - Fitzpatrick to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, December 21, 1945; 7. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 7)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding Local 601 and Westinghouse Conference, December 21, 1945; 8. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 8)
    - Fitzpatrick to Walter Mugford, et al., Regarding Westinghouse and General Electric Strikes, December 26, 1945; 9. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 9)
    - Fitzpatrick to Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, February 14, 1946; 10. (Box 2, Folder 61, Item 10)